Karanveer Singh

Personal info

Experienced User Interface Designer

My knowledge about the user centered interface has been sharpened over the years. I am open for collaborations and team work to reach desired ambitions. I've gained a wealth of expertise by working on a wide variety of projects. In a nutshell - you'll love me to be part of your team.

★ karanveer75singh@gmail.com	Mohali, India
+91 855 795 6466	My Portfolio
LinkedIn Profile	
My skills	
Primary: Figma	a
Secondary: Photo	oshop, HTML, CSS, SCSS
Recent roles: User I	Interface Designer
	sh - full working proficiency bi - native - limited working proficiency

French - A1

Work Experience

Career

UX/UI Designer

Netpyx • Full time 2012 - 2018

- Delivered numerous projects.
- Helped my company to earn two loyal clients in the first year of my job.
- Collaborated with team leader and product manager on weekly revisions of an on going project.
- Revamped mobile sites to help clients build a better user experience for their customers.
- Coordinated with web developers for site development, by providing them with assets like images, icons, size guides etc.
- Senior instructor for Web design interns for one year.

Junior Designer

Optimum Technologies • Internship Aug 2011 - Dec 2011

- Assisting the senior designer in implementing design solutions for websites and web applications.
- Designing wireframes in Photoshop.

Education

College

B-Tech in Computer Science and Engg.

Institute of Engineering & Technology IET Bhaddal 2007 - 2011

Certifications

Google UX Design Professional Certificate

Coursera

2022

Enterprise Design Thinking - Practitioner

IBM

2022

Do you like my profile? Reach out!

I am waiting for the next challlenge.

Hire me